(Sheldon:)So I guess there's two things
I can't tell you.
(Leonard:)I wish there were more.
(Sheldon:)Good night.
(Sheldon:)- I'm sorry, this is really important.
- What is it?
(Sheldon:)I like the Transformers.
(Sheldon:)Do you like the Transformers?
(Leonard:)Where exactly did your mother
have you tested?
(Bernadette:)Leonard.
(Sheldon:)The Transformers teach us that things
are not always what they appear to be.
You know, like a...
A semi-truck might be an alien robot...
(Sheldon:)...or, uh, someone
in a romantic relationship...
(Sheldon:)...might feel differently
than they appear to.
(Sheldon:)Or a conversation
about the Transformers...
(Sheldon:)...might actually be about someone
in this room.